<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2018 Google Inc.
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Manchester United F.C.</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Manchester United Football Club </string>
    <string name="article_text"> Manchester United Football Club is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England,
\n\n
that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football. Nicknamed "the Red Devils", the club was
\n\n
founded as Newton Heath LYR Football Club in 1878, changed its name to Manchester United in 1902 and moved to its
\n\n
current stadium, Old Trafford, in 1910. Manchester United have won more trophies than any other club in English
\n\n
football, with a record 20 League titles, 12 FA Cups, five League Cups and a record 21 FA Community Shields.
\n\n
United have also won three UEFA Champions Leagues, one UEFA Europa League, one UEFA Cup Winners Cup, one UEFA Super
\n\n
Cup, one Intercontinental Cup and one FIFA Club World Cup. In 1998–99, the club became the first in the history of
\n\n
English football to achieve the continental European treble. By winning the UEFA Europa League in 2016–17, they
\n\n
became one of five clubs to have won all three main UEFA club competitions.Manchester United was the highest-earning football club in the world for 2016–17, with an annual revenue of €676.3 million, and the worlds third most valuable football club in 2019, valued at £3.15 billion ($3.81 billion). After being floated on the London Stock Exchange in 1991, the club was taken private after a purchase by Malcolm Glazer in 2005 at almost £800 million, of which over £500 million of borrowed money became the clubs debt. From 2012, some shares of the club were listed on the New York Stock Exchange, although the Glazer family retains overall ownership and control of the club. Alex Ferguson and his assistant Archie Knox arrived from Aberdeen on the day of Atkinsons dismissal, and guided the club to an 11th-place finish in the league. Despite a second-place finish in 1987–88, the club was back in 11th place the following season. Reportedly on the verge of being dismissed, victory over Crystal Palace in the 1990 FA Cup Final replay (after a 3–3 draw) saved Fergusons career. The following season, Manchester United claimed its first Cup Winners Cup title and competed in the 1991 UEFA Super Cup, beating European Cup holders Red Star Belgrade 1–0 in the final at Old Trafford. A second consecutive League Cup final appearance followed in 1992, in which the team beat Nottingham Forest 1–0 at Wembley. In 1993, the club won its first league title since 1967, and a year later, for the first time since 1957, it won a second consecutive title – alongside the FA Cup – to complete the first "Double" in the club's history. United then became the first English club to do the Double twice when they won both competition0s again in 1995–96, before retaining the league title once more in 1996–97 with a game to spare. Front three: Manchester United's treble medals of the 1998–99 season are displayed at the club's museum.
In the 1998–99 season, Manchester United became the first team to win the Premier League, FA Cup and UEFA Champions League – "The Treble" – in the same season. Losing 1–0 going into injury time in the 1999 UEFA Champions League Final, Teddy Sheringham and Ole Gunnar Solskjær scored late goals to claim a dramatic victory over Bayern Munich, in what is considered one of the greatest comebacks of all time. The club also won the Intercontinental Cup after beating Palmeiras 1–0 in Tokyo. Ferguson was subsequently knighted for his services to football.
</string>
</resources>







